ACCION International Records MS196
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Communications and External Affairs records, 1950 -- 2012; 1985 -- 2005; MS196.006; 62.7 Linear Feet; 238 Audiovisual Object(s); 365 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographs and audiovisual materials, 1950 -- 2009; 1980 -- 2005; MS196.006.006; 25.3 Linear Feet; 357 Digital Object(s)
    - Robin Photos, Untitled 4, 1960 -- 1999; MS196.006.00354
    - Robin Photos, Untitled 5, 1960 -- 1999; MS196.006.00355
    - Robin Photos, Untitled 6, 1960 -- 1999; MS196.006.00356
    - Robin Photos, Untitled 7, 1960 -- 1999; MS196.006.00357
    - Winnie original 3, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.00358
    - Africa delegation - ACCION in the field, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00001 (Box 68)
    - India, 2006 -- 2007; MS196.006.006.068.00002 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Cotonou, Benin (1 of 3), 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00003 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Cotonou, Benin (2 of 3), 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00004 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Cotonou, Benin (3 of 3), 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00005 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Porto Novo, Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00006 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Parakou, Benin (1 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00007 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Parakou, Benin (1 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00008 (Box 68)
    - Bank scenes - PADME, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00009 (Box 68)
    - Market scenes - Parakou, Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00010 (Box 68)
    - Market scenes - Cotonou, Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00011 (Box 68)
    - Market scenes - Porto Novo, Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00012 (Box 68)
    - Products - Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00013 (Box 68)
    - Kids - Benin, 2002; MS196.006.006.068.00014 (Box 68)
    - PADME - Benin proof sheets, 2002 -- 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00015 (Box 68)
    - PADME bank branch - Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00016 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Aloomey, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00017 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Azov&#232, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00018 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Cotonou, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00019 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Parakou, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00020 (Box 68)
    - PADME clients - Porto Novo, Benin, 2006; MS196.006.006.068.00021 (Box 68)
    - Uganda - Markets and people, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00022 (Box 68)
    - Children in Uganda - Sudanese refugee children, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00023 (Box 68)
    - Children in Uganda, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00024 (Box 68)
    - UMV Branch - Kasanganti, Uganda, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00025 (Box 68)
    - UMV Branch/Bank photos - Victoria White and UMV staff, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00026 (Box 68)
    - UMV Branch - Adjumani, Uganda, 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00027 (Box 68)
    - Uganda Microfinance Union clients (1 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00028 (Box 68)
    - Uganda Microfinance Union clients (2 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00029 (Box 68)
    - Uganda Microfinance Union clients (3 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.068.00030 (Box 68)
    - Ambiente, Tanzania, 2005; MS196.006.006.068.00031 (Box 68)
    - Akiba, Tanzania clients, 2005; MS196.006.006.068.00032 (Box 68)
    - TCHUMA (Mozambique) - clients, 2001 -- 2002; MS196.006.006.069.00001 (Box 69)
    - TCHUMA (Mozambique) - clients (1 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00002 (Box 69)
    - TCHUMA (Mozambique) - clients (2 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00003 (Box 69)
    - TCHUMA (Mozambique) - clients (3 of 3), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00004 (Box 69)
    - Markets, people, and children (Mozambique), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00005 (Box 69)
    - Mozambique - hands, products, and resident advisors, 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00006 (Box 69)
    - MicroKing Finance - Zimbabwe, 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00007 (Box 69)
    - Unidentified photograph, 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00008 (Box 69)
    - Children - Aint'l, 2000; MS196.006.006.069.00009 (Box 69)
    - Master slide show, 1997; MS196.006.006.069.00010 (Box 69)
    - Colombia, 1990 -- 1991; MS196.006.006.069.00011 (Box 69)
    - Argentina - Emprender clients, 1997; MS196.006.006.069.00012 (Box 69)
    - PRODEM clients, 1995 -- 1998; MS196.006.006.069.00013 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - non-clients, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.069.00014 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia Ambiente, 1986 -- 1997; MS196.006.006.069.00015 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - bank shots and training, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.069.00016 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - clients, program unknown, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.069.00017 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.006.069.00018 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol (1 of 5), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00019 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol (2 of 5), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00020 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol (3 of 5), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00021 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol (4 of 5), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00022 (Box 69)
    - Bolivia - Bancosol (5 of 5), 2003; MS196.006.006.069.00023 (Box 69)
    - Brazil - CrediAmigo clients, 2007; MS196.006.006.069.00024 (Box 69)
    - Brazil - non-clients, 2001; MS196.006.006.070.00001 (Box 70)
    - Brazil - Ambiente, 2001; MS196.006.006.070.00002 (Box 70)
    - Brazil (1 of 2), 1998 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.070.00003 (Box 70)
    - Brazil (2 of 2), 1999 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.070.00004 (Box 70)
    - Brazil - Fenape clients, 1999; MS196.006.006.070.00005 (Box 70)
    - Chile - Rabin, 2000; MS196.006.006.070.00006 (Box 70)
    - Chile - Propesa, 1993; MS196.006.006.070.00007 (Box 70)
    - Christi's trip to Haiti (1 of 2), 2003; MS196.006.006.070.00008 (Box 70)
    - Christi's trip to Haiti (2 of 2), 2003; MS196.006.006.070.00009 (Box 70)
    - Guatemala non-clients, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00010 (Box 70)
    - Ecuador delegation, 2003; MS196.006.006.070.00011 (Box 70)
    - CrediFe clients, 2004; MS196.006.006.070.00012 (Box 70)
    - Ecuador - bank photos and training, 1998; MS196.006.006.070.00013 (Box 70)
    - Dominican Republic non-clients, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00014 (Box 70)
    - Dominican Republic clients, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00015 (Box 70)
    - Ambiente - Dominican Republic, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00016 (Box 70)
    - Colombia non-clients, 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.070.00017 (Box 70)
    - Finansol - Colombia, 1997; MS196.006.006.070.00018 (Box 70)
    - Fundaci&#242n Mario Santo Domingo, 1997 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.070.00019 (Box 70)
    - FMSD clients, 1997 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.070.00020 (Box 70)
    - Dialogo and miscellaneous - Colombia, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00021 (Box 70)
    - Colombia - Ambiente, 1997 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.070.00022 (Box 70)
    - Cooperativa Emprender clients, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00023 (Box 70)
    - Finamerica clients, 1997 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.070.00024 (Box 70)
    - Ecuador - non-clients, 1985 -- 1998; MS196.006.006.070.00025 (Box 70)
    - Banco Solidario clients - Ecuador (1 of 5), 1998 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.070.00026 (Box 70)
    - Banco Solidario clients - Ecuador (2 of 5), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.070.00027 (Box 70)
    - Banco Solidario clients - Ecuador (3 of 5), 1990 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00001 (Box 71)
    - Banco Solidario clients - Ecuador (4 of 5), 1990 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00002 (Box 71)
    - Banco Solidario clients - Ecuador (5 of 5), 1998 -- 2002; MS196.006.006.071.00003 (Box 71)
    - Ecuador - Ambiente, 1998; MS196.006.006.071.00004 (Box 71)
    - FED clients, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.006.071.00005 (Box 71)
    - Guatemala - Ambiente (1 of 2), 1990 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00006 (Box 71)
    - Guatemala - Ambiente (2 of 2), 1992 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00007 (Box 71)
    - Genesis clients - Guatemala (1 of 3), 1991 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00008 (Box 71)
    - Genesis clients - Guatemala (2 of 3), 1998 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.071.00009 (Box 71)
    - Genesis clients - Guatemala (3 of 3), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.071.00010 (Box 71)
    - Clients, program unknown - Guatemala, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.071.00011 (Box 71)
    - BCP clients - Honduras, 2007; MS196.006.006.071.00012 (Box 71)
    - Honduras Ambiente, 1998 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.071.00013 (Box 71)
    - Honduras non-clients (1 of 2), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.071.00014 (Box 71)
    - Honduras non-clients (2 of 2), 1998; MS196.006.006.071.00015 (Box 71)
    - FINSOL - Honduras, 1998 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.071.00016 (Box 71)
    - Ambiente - El Salvador, 2002; MS196.006.006.071.00017 (Box 71)
    - Integral - El Salvador (1 of 4), 2002; MS196.006.006.071.00018 (Box 71)
    - Integral - El Salvador (2 of 4), 2002; MS196.006.006.071.00019 (Box 71)
    - Integral - El Salvador (3 of 4), 2002; MS196.006.006.071.00020 (Box 71)
    - Integral - El Salvador (4 of 4), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00001 (Box 72)
    - El Salvador (1 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00002 (Box 72)
    - El Salvador (2 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00003 (Box 72)
    - Fundap clients (1 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00004 (Box 72)
    - Fundap clients (2 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00005 (Box 72)
    - Haiti, miscellaneous, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00006 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (1 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00007 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (2 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00008 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (3 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00009 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (4 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00010 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (5 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00011 (Box 72)
    - SogeSol clients (6 of 6), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00012 (Box 72)
    - Ambiente, Haiti and non-clients (1 of 2), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00013 (Box 72)
    - Ambiente, Haiti and non-clients (2 of 2), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.072.00014 (Box 72)
    - Compartamos - Mexico, solidarity groups and non-client photos (1 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00015 (Box 72)
    - Compartamos - Mexico, solidarity groups and non-client photos (2 of 2), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00016 (Box 72)
    - ADMIC - Mexico, 1998; MS196.006.006.072.00017 (Box 72)
    - Ambiente, Panama, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.072.00018 (Box 72)
    - Multicredit - ACCION Empresarial, Panama, 1995; MS196.006.006.072.00019 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients (1 of 5), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00020 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients (2 of 5), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00021 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients (3 of 5), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00022 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients (4 of 5), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00023 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients (5 of 5), 2002; MS196.006.006.072.00024 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, FAMA clients, 2007; MS196.006.006.072.00025 (Box 72)
    - Nicaragua, Ambiente, 1998 -- 2002; MS196.006.006.073.00001 (Box 73)
    - Nicaragua non-clients, 1998; MS196.006.006.073.00002 (Box 73)
    - Mexico non-clients, 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00003 (Box 73)
    - Mexico - Ambiente, 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00004 (Box 73)
    - Paraguay - Ambiente, 1997; MS196.006.006.073.00005 (Box 73)
    - Fundaci&#242n Paraguay clients, 1997; MS196.006.006.073.00006 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (1 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.073.00007 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (2 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.073.00008 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (3 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.073.00009 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (4 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.073.00010 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (5 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.073.00011 (Box 73)
    - Ambiente, Peru (1 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00012 (Box 73)
    - Ambiente, Peru (2 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00013 (Box 73)
    - Peru non-clients (1 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00014 (Box 73)
    - Peru non-clients (2 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00015 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (1 of 5), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00016 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (2 of 5), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00017 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (3 of 5), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00018 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (4 of 5), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00019 (Box 73)
    - Milbanco, Peru (5 of 5), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.073.00020 (Box 73)
    - Client/program unknown - Peru, 2001; MS196.006.006.073.00021 (Box 73)
    - Peru, bank shots and training, 1998; MS196.006.006.073.00022 (Box 73)
    - Bagente, Venezuela (1 of 4), 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00023 (Box 73)
    - Bagente, Venezuela (2 of 4), 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00024 (Box 73)
    - Bagente, Venezuela (3 of 4), 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00025 (Box 73)
    - Bagente, Venezuela (4 of 4), 2000; MS196.006.006.073.00026 (Box 73)
    - Mexico - Ambiente, 2000; MS196.006.006.074.00001 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (1 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00002 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (2 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00003 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (3 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00004 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (4 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00005 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (5 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00006 (Box 74)
    - Compartamos - Mexico clients (6 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.006.074.00007 (Box 74)
    - Staff - countries Costa Rica to Guatemala, 1990; MS196.006.006.074.00008 (Box 74)
    - Staff - countries Argentina to Colombia, 1995; MS196.006.006.074.00009 (Box 74)
    - Portraits, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.074.00010 (Box 74)
    - Man with telescope, 1998; MS196.006.006.074.00011 (Box 74)
    - Portrait photographs, 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.074.00012 (Box 74)
    - ACCION USA staff (1 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00013 (Box 74)
    - ACCION USA staff (2 of 2), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00014 (Box 74)
    - Bank pictures, 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00015 (Box 74)
    - Borrowers and loan officers, 2000; MS196.006.006.074.00016 (Box 74)
    - Animals, 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00017 (Box 74)
    - Presidential awards, 1997; MS196.006.006.074.00018 (Box 74)
    - Families - Latin America, 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00019 (Box 74)
    - Gift photos, 1980 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.074.00020 (Box 74)
    - Children (1 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00021 (Box 74)
    - Children (2 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.074.00022 (Box 74)
    - Children (3 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00001 (Box 75)
    - Children (4 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00002 (Box 75)
    - Children (5 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00003 (Box 75)
    - Children (6 of 6), 2000 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00004 (Box 75)
    - Peru and Ecuador (1 of 3), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00005 (Box 75)
    - Peru and Ecuador (2 of 3), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00006 (Box 75)
    - Peru and Ecuador (3 of 3), 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00007 (Box 75)
    - Latin America, 1955 -- 1981; MS196.006.006.075.00008 (Box 75)
    - Latin America - various places and people, 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.075.00009 (Box 75)
    - Paraguay, 1986; MS196.006.006.075.00010 (Box 75)
    - Latin America - various places and people, 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.075.00011 (Box 75)
    - Dominican Republic workshop, 1991; MS196.006.006.075.00012 (Box 75)
    - ACCION international staff/VIPs, 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00013 (Box 75)
    - Hands/working, 1995 -- 2005; MS196.006.006.075.00014 (Box 75)
    - Maria Otero (1 of 3), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00015 (Box 75)
    - Maria Otero (2 of 3), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00016 (Box 75)
    - Maria Otero (3 of 3), 2000; MS196.006.006.075.00017 (Box 75)
    - Palm Pilots: Mexico and Ecuador, 2003; MS196.006.006.075.00018 (Box 75)
    - Board/Presidents Council photos, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00019 (Box 75)
    - Staff - Cambridge and Washington (1 of 3), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.075.00020 (Box 75)
    - Staff - Cambridge and Washington (2 of 3), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.075.00021 (Box 75)
    - Staff - Cambridge and Washington (3 of 3), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.075.00022 (Box 75)
    - Staff in the field (1 of 2), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00023 (Box 75)
    - Staff in the field (1 of 2), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00024 (Box 75)
    - Staff - U.S. Programs, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00025 (Box 75)
    - ACCION parties and events (1 of 5), 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.075.00026 (Box 75)
    - ACCION parties and events (2 of 5), 1992 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.076.00001 (Box 76)
    - ACCION parties and events (3 of 5), 1991 -- 1998; MS196.006.006.076.00002 (Box 76)
    - ACCION parties and events (4 of 5), 2001; MS196.006.006.076.00003 (Box 76)
    - ACCION parties and events (5 of 5), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.076.00004 (Box 76)
    - Citibank, 2001; MS196.006.006.076.00005 (Box 76)
    - Joke photos, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.076.00006 (Box 76)
    - Delegation - Nicaragua and Honduras, 1998; MS196.006.006.076.00007 (Box 76)
    - Delegation - Argentina and Paraguay negatives, 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00008 (Box 76)
    - Delegation - Argentina contact sheets, 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00009 (Box 76)
    - Delegation - Argentina and Paraguay, 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00010 (Box 76)
    - Staff conferences (1 of 2), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.076.00011 (Box 76)
    - Staff conferences (2 of 2), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.076.00012 (Box 76)
    - Fundraising Guatemala (1 of 2), 1994; MS196.006.006.076.00013 (Box 76)
    - Fundraising Guatemala (2 of 2), 1994; MS196.006.006.076.00014 (Box 76)
    - U.S. Summit with awards, 1996; MS196.006.006.076.00015 (Box 76)
    - Microcredit Summit (1 of 3), 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00016 (Box 76)
    - Microcredit Summit (2 of 3), 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00017 (Box 76)
    - Microcredit Summit (3 of 3), 1997; MS196.006.006.076.00018 (Box 76)
    - Mexico (1 of 2), 2001; MS196.006.006.076.00019 (Box 76)
    - Mexico (2 of 2), 2001; MS196.006.006.076.00020 (Box 76)
    - Other Latin America, 1980 -- 1989; MS196.006.006.076.00021 (Box 76)
    - Latin America - special events and inaugurations (1 of 2), 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.076.00022 (Box 76)
    - Latin America - special events and inaugurations (2 of 2), 1980 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.076.00023 (Box 76)
    - Visits and delegations (1 of 2), 1987 -- 1992; MS196.006.006.076.00024 (Box 76)
    - Visits and delegations (2 of 2), 1988 -- 1991; MS196.006.006.076.00025 (Box 76)
    - Fundraising Ecuador (1 of 4), 1993; MS196.006.006.076.00026 (Box 76)
    - Fundraising Ecuador (2 of 4), 1993; MS196.006.006.077.00001 (Box 77)
    - Fundraising Ecuador (3 of 4), 1993; MS196.006.006.077.00002 (Box 77)
    - Fundraising Ecuador (4 of 4), 1993; MS196.006.006.077.00003 (Box 77)
    - Award dinners and events, 1991 -- 1995; MS196.006.006.077.00004 (Box 77)
    - Peru delegation, 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00005 (Box 77)
    - Costa Rica workshop photos, 1980 -- 1989; MS196.006.006.077.00006 (Box 77)
    - ACCION reunion (1 of 3), 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00007 (Box 77)
    - ACCION reunion (2 of 3), 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00008 (Box 77)
    - ACCION reunion (3 of 3), 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00009 (Box 77)
    - Awards dinner - Boston, 1995; MS196.006.006.077.00010 (Box 77)
    - ACCION Texas delegation (1 of 2), 1997; MS196.006.006.077.00011 (Box 77)
    - ACCION Texas delegation (2 of 2), 1997; MS196.006.006.077.00012 (Box 77)
    - Delegation Peru (1 of 2), 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00013 (Box 77)
    - Delegation Peru (2 of 2), 1996; MS196.006.006.077.00014 (Box 77)
    - Delegation Bolivia, 1995; MS196.006.006.077.00015 (Box 77)
    - Delegation Ecuador, 1993; MS196.006.006.077.00016 (Box 77)
    - Donor - Ron Livingston, 2004; MS196.006.006.077.00017 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (1 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00018 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (2 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00019 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (3 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00020 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (4 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00021 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (5 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00022 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (6 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00023 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (7 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00024 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (8 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00025 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (9 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00026 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (10 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00027 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (11 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00028 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (12 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.077.00029 (Box 77)
    - Delegation photos (13 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00001 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (14 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00002 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (15 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00003 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (16 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00004 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (17 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00005 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (18 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00006 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (19 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00007 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (20 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00008 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (21 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00009 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (22 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00010 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (23 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00011 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (24 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00012 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (25 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00013 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (26 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00014 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos (27 of 27), 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00015 (Box 78)
    - Photographs, slides, and correspondence, 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.078.00016 (Box 78)
    - Photos of artwork, director's conference, 1991 -- 1995; MS196.006.006.078.00017 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos - Quito, Ecuador, 1999; MS196.006.006.078.00018 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos - chickens and people, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00019 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos - woman with tortillas, 1990 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00020 (Box 78)
    - Photos to Roy Jacobowitz from Citigroup Foundation, 2000; MS196.006.006.078.00021 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos - Paraguay, Fundaci&#242n, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00022 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos, individual photos, 2000 -- 2009; MS196.006.006.078.00023 (Box 78)
    - Delegation photos - Nicaragua and Honduras, 1998; MS196.006.006.078.00024 (Box 78)
    - Mexico delegation (1 of 2), 2000; MS196.006.006.079.00001 (Box 79)
    - Mexico delegation (2 of 2), 2000; MS196.006.006.079.00002 (Box 79)
    - Directors conferences, 1995 -- 2000; MS196.006.006.079.00003 (Box 79)
    - Working Capital photographs (1 of 2), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.079.00004 (Box 79)
    - Working Capital photographs (2 of 2), 1990 -- 1999; MS196.006.006.079.00005 (Box 79)
    - Fiestas, inaugurations, graduations, 1962; MS196.006.006.079.00006 (Box 79)
    - The people, 1963; MS196.006.006.079.00007 (Box 79)
    - Classes, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00008 (Box 79)
    - Crafts, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00009 (Box 79)
    - Publicity, 1962; MS196.006.006.079.00010 (Box 79)
    - Work in progress (small prints), 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00011 (Box 79)
    - Hirschmann, Ralph and Lucy, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00012 (Box 79)
    - Lunchtime in the barrio, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00013 (Box 79)
    - Various - archives, 1960 -- 1979; MS196.006.006.079.00014 (Box 79)
    - Athletics, 1960 -- 1969; MS196.006.006.079.00015 (Box 79)